

Around 3 years of professional IT Experience as a Software Developer in Ncr corporation.



Current Designation: Software Engineer Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 10 Month(s)

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Pref. Location: Hyderabad Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: SQL Server, TFS, C#, ASP. Net MVC, WPF, MVVM, Web API, . Net Core

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21 Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Summary

Around 3 years of professional IT Experience as a Software Developer. Worked in an Agile environment. Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams. Extensively utilized Object Oriented Programming and Design Patterns. Experienced in Microsoft technologies - .NET Framework, .Net Core, ASP.NET, WPF, SQL Server. Designed Test Cases for Unit Testing, Integrations Testing and Coded UI testing.

Work Experience

as Software Engineer Jan 2021 to Till Date

NCR Corporation India Pvt. Ltd as Dotnet developer

Dec 2017 to Oct 2020

Around 3 years of professional IT Experience as a Software Developer. Worked in an Agile environment. Effective in working independently and collaboratively in teams. Extensively utilized Object Oriented Programming and Design Patterns. Experienced in Microsoft technologies - .NET Framework, .Net Core, ASP.NET, WPF, SQL Server. Designed Test Cases for Unit Testing, Integrations Testing and Coded UI testing.

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Indira Gandhi Institute of Technology, Dhenkanal in 2017

IT Skills

Skill Name Version Last Used **Experience** 1/22/2021 https://freesearch.naukri.com/preview/printResume?uname=21cd95c2ae0e59229897266334cfea750d0f5802424758170047435d55...

C#.NET, .Net Core		
SQL Server		
ASP.Net MVC		
Web API		

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				
Odia				

Projects

Project Title: Emerald Point Of Sale

Client: North gate

Nature of Employment: Full Time Duration: May 2019 - Oct 2020

Project Location: Hyderabad Onsite / Offsite: Onsite Role: Programmer Team Size: 30

Skill Used: C#, ASP.Net MVC, SQL Server, .Net core, Web API, MVVM, WPF

Role Description: Dotnet developer

Project Details: Project Overview: The cloud first enterprise POS platform that gives you everything you need to run your supermarket from POS to payments to back office, loyalty and beyond.

Retail Store Solution is a leading-edge point of sale software solution focused on the checkout marketplace. From large hypermarkets and supermarkets to small convenience stores, the primary focus of Retail Store is on the grocery, fuel POS and specialty sectors.

The solution includes a robust POS, built-in customer promotions, configurable reporting capabilities and support for both consumer and mobile POS, self-checkout, fuel and quick service POS. Designed to utilize the innovative NCR platform services.

Responsibilities:

Participated in gathering the requirements and defined the business rules to user requirements in SDLC and actively engage in technical discussions.

Worked on TFS for version control, Code Review and for automatic builds and continuous Integration. Followed Agile methodologies (Scrum).

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Category: General Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No Employment Status: Full time